<?xml version="1.0"?>
<EnemyNodes>
	<SmallCitters>	
		<Goblin>
			<Desc> The creature is small and scrawny, but is wielding a sort of barbed weapon and is waving it in a theatening matter. </Desc>
			<Name> Goblin Warrior </Name>
		</Goblin>
		<Kobold>


		</Kobold>
		<Myr>
			<Name>Myr</Name>
			<Desc> This metal being is hip hight, and wields razor sharp claws! Myr's are very skiddish, so plan carefully! </Desc>
		</Myr>
	</SmallCitters>
	<Critters>
		<Bandits>
			<Sand>
				
			</Sand>
			<forrest>
				
				
			</forrest>
			<mountain>
				
			</mountain>
			<pirate>
				
			</pirate>
			<generic>
				
			</generic>
			<skyraider>
				
			</skyraider>
		
		
		
		</Bandits>
		<Military>
			<Samurai>
				
			</Samurai>
			<Ronin>
				<Name>Ronin</Name>
				<male>
					<Desc>This Ronin looks like a normal government samurai, but he has stripped all of his affilitaions from his armour for reasons known only to him.</Desc>	
					<Armour>Half-Lamellar</Armour>
					<Weapon>Naginata</Weapon>
					<Speed>6</Speed>
					<Death>Though this ronin was battle hardened after the death of his master, his life of the wave has come to an end by your hands.</Death>
				</male>
				<female>
					<Armour>Half-Lamellar</Armour>
					<Desc>This Ronin looks like a normal government samurai, but she has stripped all of her affilitaions from her armour.</Desc>
					<Weapon>Naginata</Weapon>
					<Speed>6</Speed>
					<Death>Though this ronin was battle hardened after the death of her master, her life of the wave has come to an end by your hands.</Death>
				</female>					
			</Ronin>
			
			
		</Military>
		
	</Critters>
	<LargCritters>
		<AwakenedEarth>
			<Name>Awakened Earth</Name>
			<Desc>This pile of earth has been dormant for aeons, it has broken from the landscape to destroy Kagima's inhabitants</Desc>			
		</AwakenedEarth>

		
	</LargCritters>
	<SpecialEnimies>
		<Human>
			
			<Toshijiro>
				<Name>Hoshijiro, The Silent Wind</Name>
				<Desc>Hoshijiro is a master of nature, he keeps balance in Viria's forest, his life as a hermit has made him a force to be reckoned with. You've upset the balance, prepare to die! </Desc>
				<Armour>Bone-Lamellar</Armour>
				<Weapon>Nodachi</Weapon>
				<Speed>8</Speed>
				<Ability1>Bushido</Ability1>
				<Ability2>Nature's Force</Ability2>
				<Death>Through your skill's as a warrior, you have disruppted the balance of nature in Viria's forest, and with her keeper lying dead at your feet, the woods are sure to see a tide of change never imaginable.</Death>
			</Toshijiro>
			<Ramos>
				<Name>Ramos, Captian of Intesa</Name>
				<Desc>Ramos is the gaurd captian of Intesa, with the might of Eclasia and her armies, he has answered Shekai's call to arms against the awakening lands, you stand in his way, prepare for a fight.</Desc>
				<Armour>Full-Plate</Armour>
				<Weapon>Bastard Sword</Weapon>
				<Speed>4</Speed>
				<Ability1>Rally Call</Ability1>
				<Death>Lowering your sword to Ramos, bloody and beaten, he utters one last curse to your name before succumbing to his wounds, with blade and ranks broken, he dies as a captian of none.</Death>
				
			</Ramos>
			<Mikami>
				<Name>Mikami, Keeper of honor.</Name>
				<Desc>Mikami is agianst violence, and prefers to mend peoples wounds rather than inflicting them. But through your actions, she has taken up sacred arms to vanquish you!</Desc>
				<Armour>Full-Lamellar</Armour>
				<Weapon>Katana</Weapon>
				<Speed>6</Speed>
				<Ability1>Mending Hands</Ability1>
				<Ability2>Bushido</Ability2>
				<Death>Through combat superiortiy, you have bested Mikami, she makes a last ditch effort to save herself with her healing magic, but stops breathing before she can mend her wounds. </Death>
			</Mikami>
		</Human>
		<Skal>
			<Koshita>
				<Name>Koshita, Shekai's Messanger</Name>\
				<Desc>Koshita lives and travels to find those that will answer Shekai's call to protect Kagima from the awakening of the ancient lands</Desc>
				<Armour>Half-Lamellar</Armour>
				<Weapon>Tanto</Weapon>
				<Speed>10</Speed>
				<Ability1>Bushido</Ability1>
				<Ability2>Swift feet</Ability2>
				<Death>Though he was just as fast as the wind, Koshita dies by your hands, Shekai's protectors will be mourning the loss of thier dear rallier.</Death>
				
			</Koshita>
			
			<Shekai>
				<Name>Shekai, Caller of Armies</Name>
				<Desc>Shekai is a legendary ronin, he is here to call the world to arms against impending extinction, don't expect him to go easy on you.</Desc>
				<Armour>Half-Lamellar</Armour>
				<Weapon>Naginata</Weapon>
				<Speed>7</Speed>
				<Ablility1>Bushido</Ablility1>
				<Death>You have bested Shekai, with the only proctector laying dead at your feet the plane is doomed against the lands that have been awoken.</Death>
			</Shekai>
		</Skal>
		<Vampire>
			<Vlad>
				<Name>Vladimir Bourdreaux</Name>
				<Desc>Vladimir is a ruthless ronin and cunning vampire lord, he empowers his blade with Hakana's Grimoire, making him a deadly adversary.</Desc>
				<Armour>Studded</Armour>
				<Weapon>Magic Katana</Weapon>
				<Speed>10</Speed>
				<Death>You have bested Vladimir, battered and bloody, he congradulates you on your victory, pulls himself (literally) together and vanishes in a cloud of black magic.</Death>
			</Vlad>
		</Vampire>
		<Goblin>
			<KaiKai>
				<Name>Kai-Kai, Ronin Seeker</Name>	
				<Desc>Kai-Kai is a student of the arts of bushido, having killed multiple masters, he has not completed his training, but still seeks enlightenment, you stand between him and his goals</Desc>
				<Armour>Cloth</Armour>
				<Weapon>Tanto</Weapon>
				<Speed>9</Speed>
				<Death>Through supieror force you have defeated Kai-Kai, but he rises agian as a spirit, touched by the kami and ready to kill.</Death>		
			</KaiKai>
			<SpiritKaiKai>
				<Name>Kami touched Kai-Kai</Name>
				<Desc>The Kami has enlightened Kai-Kai in the secrets of bushido that he sought, now reformed and armed, he is ready to seek vengence.</Desc>
				<Armour>None</Armour>
				<Weapon>Etherial Tanto</Weapon>
				<Speed>10</Speed>
				<Ability1>Bushido</Ability1>
				<Death>Even the enlightenment of the Kami was not enough keep Kai-Kai from his fate, you've bested one of the best ronin in all the lands.</Death>
			</SpiritKaiKai>	
		</Goblin>
		
		
		
	</SpecialEnimies>


</EnemyNodes>